<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="button_show_changelog">Changelog</string>

    <string name="title_action_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_about_dialog">About EnigmAndroid</string>
    <string name="description_text">EnigmAndroid is an implementation of a simulation of the Enigma Machine.
    The Enigma Machine is a cypher machine developed in the 1920s. It was used by the german Wehrmacht to
    encipher secret messaged during the second world war. There were multiple different Enigma models. For enciphering text, every letter is passed through 3-4 mechanical rotors that rotate with every keystroke.
    That way the enigma achieves polyalphabetic substitution and the output appears random. The rotors could be chosen from a set of 5. Additionally there was a
    so called plugboard, where one could switch over pairs of letters.
    </string>

    <string name="title_section_how_to_use">How to use</string>
    <string name="section_how_to_use">In the beginning, choose a model of the enigma machine to work with.
        You can do this in the settings. To encrypt/decrypt a message, you can name it into the input field.
        Afterwards you can - depending on the chosen model - select a reflector and the some rotors. Also select their initial positions.
        Then you may set pairs on the plugboard or on the pluggable reflector.
        Therefore press the respective button and connect the characters you wish to connect by clicking them one after another.
        If you want to disconnect two plugs, just touch one of the plugs twice.
        Also you can optionally set custom ring settings. Open the options menu and select \"Ringsettings\".
        When you are ready press \"En-/Decrypt!\".</string>

    <string name="title_section_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="section_developer">EnigmAndroid is developed by: \nPaul Schaub</string>

    <string name="title_section_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="section_disclaimer">THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
</resources>
